ROBERT SMITH

Senior Test Lead I

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

SUMMARY

Over 14+ years of software quality and testing expertise related web, mobile, and client/server apps Over 10+ years of leadership in Senior QA roles within Testing CoE (TCoE) Broad industry experience in banking, insurance, healthcare and e-commerce Extensive exposure in Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) phases such as Requirements Analysis, Test Planning, Test Estimation, Test Execution, Test Management ,Test Closure Directed efforts for Functional.

CORE COMPETENCIES

.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Test Lead I

ABC Corporation - June 2015 - September 2015

Key Deliverables:

- Duration June 2015 September 2015 Tools Selenium, JIRA, Gomez and MS
 Office Technology/Software J2EE, HTML/CSS Project Description
 http://www.merckmillipore.com/ deals on medical products for various countries
 where end customer must select county region and choose the product of their
 choice cart and checkout.
- application is built in J2EE, HTML/CSS.
- Decision Tree, Smoke and Regression testing were performed for each release.
- Responsibilities Responsible for final approval of all eCommerce application deliverables Followed Agile methodology to promote rapid deliveries and near-zero defect counts Onsite-Offshore coordination with testing team of size 10.
- Coordinated Test Planning with subject matter experts (SME) and other key stakeholders Worked on Requirements Analysis and Test Planning with the client Managed Automated Test suites in Selenium for the Smoke Tests and Regression Tests Synchronized all testing activities to latest requirements.
- Managing the Functional scenarios, including critical edge cases Involved managing and reviewing Test Plans, Test Strategy and Test Cases.
- Involved managing Requirements Traceability Matrix.

Senior Test Lead I

Delta Corporation - 2011 - 2015

Key Deliverables:

Duration April 2015 - June 2015 Tools HP ALM and MS Office
 Technology/Software J2EE, HTML/CSS Project & Description
 http//www.bestbuy.com/ deals on consumer electronics for various countries

ROBERT SMITH

Senior Test Lead I

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

where the end customer must select the county region and choose the product of their choice and add it to cart and checkout.

- Good deals are given to consumers during certain period.
- The application is built in J2EE.
- Responsibilities As a Senior Test Lead was responsible for high quality deliverables for eCommerce application which the team worked.
- Managed Smoke Tests and System Test efforts.
- Worked with SMEs in getting requirements Onsite-Offshore coordination with testing team of size 15.
- Worked on Requirements Analysis and Test Planning with the client Involved in managing Requirements Tractability Matrix which had high complex business scenarios Involved in managing and reviewing Test Plans, Test Strategy and Test Cases.

EDUCATION

Master's in Computer Application - (University of Madras)